<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title><![CDATA[Something & Anything]]></title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[The blog of hy9be@github.com]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://hy9be.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-07T22:53:47.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://hy9be.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[hy9be@github.com]]></name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title><![CDATA[Hello world]]></title>
    <link href="http://hy9be.github.io/2015/09/07/Hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://hy9be.github.io/2015/09/07/Hello-world/</id>
    <published>2015-09-07T22:02:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2015-09-07T22:53:47.000Z</updated>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I joined a group on <a href="http://www.coach.me" target="_blank" rel="external">http://www.coach.me</a>  named “#500WD” today, and will start to write something periodically (I do not want to set a hard goal of 7 days a week and 500 words each time, but I will try to write as much as possible).</p>
<p>I will write mainly in English. I am very lucky as a foreigner staying at the United States: I have a large group of Chinese friends; my manager and most of my colleagues speaks Chinese; I have easy access to all kinds of Chinese supermarket and restaurants; … As a result, I do not really feel the lonely of staying abroad alone. But I feel I took too much advantages on these lucky things and is implicitly taking very high risk of losing them. I must be prepared in case these are all taken away from me some day. To write a blog in English is a start point.</p>
<p>The content will be various. I am a geek, a top Chinese singer, a readingholic, a 15 year fan of basketball, and many more…I will write anything I like, hate or feel indifferent.</p>
<p>I do not plan to buy a domain name for this blog, though blogs on *.github.io domain names usually are focusing on programming.</p>
<p>Okay, I guess this is already pretty long for a post named “Hello, word”.</p>
]]></content>
    <summary type="html">
    <![CDATA[<p>I joined a group on <a href="http://www.coach.me" target="_blank" rel="external">http://www.coach.me</a>  named “#500WD” today, and will ]]>
    </summary>
    
      <category term="miscellaneous" scheme="http://hy9be.github.io/tags/miscellaneous/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
